Finding Aid for David E. Davis papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Speeches 1968-2009
  - 1990-1994
    - Range Rover speech, Atlanta February 9, 1991 (Box 10)
    - J.D. Power February 19, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Lincoln-Mercury Dealers April 17, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Murdoch Farewell speech, New York 21 Club June 13, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Phil Guarascio Roast June 28, 1991 (Box 10)
    - New York University speech to journalism students July 10, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Rotary Club of Pacific Grove August 13, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Gene Butera Retirement Party August 29, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Marty Singerman's Retirement Party, New York City November 22, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Society of Automotive Engineers speech December 4, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Washington Automotive Press Association, National Press Club, Washington, DC January 17, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Toast to Warren Weith, WAPA, Washington, DC January 17, 1992 (Box 10)
    - U[niversity?] of M[ichigan?] Automotive Society March 19, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Tom Adams notes, Menniger Foundation May 11, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Las Vegas International Motor Show May 12-17, 1992 (Box 10)
    - PR Society of Detroit speech May 19, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Toyota (management) speech, CA June 10, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Trant Jarman Eulogy July 12, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Adweek speech, Troy, MI September 23, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Adweek Seminar, Santa Monica, CA March 12, 1993 (Box 10)
    - David Welch Farewell, CME-KHB March 26, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Chrysler speech, Port Huron, MI February 22, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Ferrari Club of America, Chicago, IL March 5, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Madison Avenue Sports Car Chowder Society March 8, 1994 (Box 10)
    - BMW Car Club of America, Oktoberfest, Boston August 17, 1994 (Box 10)
    - IDSA (Industrial Designers Society of America) Design Conference August 20, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Jaguar Paris Dealer Launch, X300 business meeting August 26, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Speedy Muffler King Senior Manager meeting, Alberta September 18, 1994 (Box 10)
  - 1995-1999
    - Janet Schroeder Eulogy January 12, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Arne Gittleman Retirement Roast, Bloomfield Hills Country Club April 18, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Toyota Leadership Board, West Palm Beach, FL April 22, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Automotive Hall of Fame, Legends and Leaders Luncheon, Dearborn Inn June 19, 1996 (Box 10)
    - VDO speech, Winchester, VA August 2, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Automobile of the Year award presentation, Dearborn, MI November 26, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Toyota Auto Show Sales Rally, Detroit, MI January 10, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Swedish Chamber of Commerce, Forest Hills Country Club April 29, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Ferrari Club National Meeting, Landsdown Conference Center May 24, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Motorsports Hall of Fame, Annual Induction June 4, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Northwood University Auto Show speech October 10, 1997 (Box 10)
    - IAMC speech December 2-4, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Toyota speech March 17, 1998 (Box 10)
    - SCCA speech November 21, 1998 (Box 10)
    - J.D. Power 1999 (Box 10)
    - All-Stars speech, January [?] 1999 (Box 10)
    - Automotive Advertising Strategy Conference February 1999 (Box 10)
    - Toyota speech, Cape Cod, MA May 26-27, 1999 (Box 10)
    - The Grand Experience, Kalamazoo, MI June 4-6, 1999 (Box 10)
    - Motor Sports Hall of Fame speech, Detroit, MI June 10, 1999 (Box 10)
  - 2000-2004
    - Land Rover/NADA speech circa January 2000 (Box 10)
      (originally with a computer disc labeled "Toyota/Land Rover speech, 1/14/00"; see Removable Storage Media series)
    - J.D. Power/NADA speech January 21, 2000 (Box 10)
    - Dodge Dealers, Scottsdale, AZ January 18, 2001 (Box 10)
    - World Research Group Conference, Beverly Hills, CA May 21, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Greenwich Concours June 2, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Ward's 10 Engines January 2002 (Box 10)
    - Leon Mandel eulogy March 11, 2002 (Box 10)
    - Carroll Shelby VIR, Spring 2002 (Box 10)
    - IMPA speech regarding Primedia, Fall 2002 (Box 10)
    - Jaguar Dealers XJ introduction, Scottsdale, AZ March 22, 2003 (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan commencement May 1, 2004, 2 folders (Box 11)
      (second folder formerly in a binder)
    - Maybach ramblings, Greenwich July 2004 (Box 11)
      (formerly in binder)
    - Unknown audience circa November 2004 (Box 11)
  - 2005-2009
    - GMAC/MIC speech August 2005 (Box 11)
    - Beavers at D.A.C. November 3, 2005 (Box 11)
    - Detroit Athletic Club November 2005 (Box 11)
    - Porsche Club May 10, 2006 (Box 11)
    - Greenwich Concours, June [?] 2006 (Box 11)
    - University Commons July 10, 2006 (Box 11)
    - Classic Car Club speech February 15, 2007 (Box 11)
      (first page only)
    - Synergy speech, Lansing, MI April 25, 2007 (Box 11)
    - Porsche 365 July 2007 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, Meadowbrook August 4, 2007 (Box 11)
    - Kiwanis speech, Ann Arbor, MI April 20, 2008 (Box 11)
    - Speech about Karl Ludvigsen, Automotive Hall of Fame July 26, 2008 (Box 11)
    - GM Retirees speech, Charlevoix, MI September 10, 2009 (Box 11)
  - Undated speeches
    - Porsche speech (Box 11)
    - Renault Dealers speech (Box 11)
    - SCCA speeches (4) (Box 11)
    - "Stop in to any movie house today..." (Box 11)
    - Traverse City speech (Box 11)
  - Other speech-related materials
    - Clippings and other materials for speech research 1989-1990 (Box 11)
    - Draft[?] of speech undated (Box 11)
    - Note cards for a speech circa 2001 (Box 11)
- Events 1977-2000
  The Events series includes programs, correspondence, and other material related to events David E. Davis attended or hosted, ranging from car shows and races to personal events. The series is arranged in subseries alphabetically by type of event. The individual subseries are arranged chronologically with the exception of the miscellaneous subseries, which is arranged alphabetically by description.
  - Auto shows
    - Geneva Auto Show March 1977 (Box 11)
    - Frankfurt Motor Show September 1977 (Box 11)
    - New York Auto Show April 1998 (Box 11)
    - Detroit Auto Show January 1999 (Box 11)
    - Geneva Auto Show March 1999 (Box 11)
    - New York International Auto Show April 1999 (Box 11)
  - Concours d'Elegance
    - Pebble Beach Concours August 1996 (Box 11)
    - Chrysler-Louis Vuitton Concours, New York City September 1996 (Box 11)
    - Louis Vuitton Classic September 1997 (Box 11)
    - Amelia Island Concours April 1998, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Ault Park Concours June 1998 (Box 11)
    - Amelia Island Concours March 1999 (Box 11)
    - Pebble Beach Concours August 1999 (Box 11)
    - Louis Vuitton Classic September 1999 (Box 12)
    - Castle Hill Concours September 1999 (Box 12)
    - Ault Park Concours June 1999 (Box 12)
  - Eyes on the Classics
    - June 1993 (Box 12)
    - June 1994 (Box 12)
    - June 1995 (Box 12)
  - Grand Prix and other car races
    - Pittsburgh Grand Prix 1988 (Box 12)
    - Rolex 24 at Daytona February 1992, January 1993 (Box 12)
    - Pittsburgh Vintage Grand Prix July 1994 (Box 12)
    - Rolex 24 at Daytona January 1999 (Box 12)
    - Grand Prix de Monaco May 1999 (Box 12)
  - Mille Miglia
    - Italy 1988 (Box 12)
    - Italy May 1992 (Box 12)
    - California September-October 1992 (Box 12)
    - California May 1994 (Box 12)
    - California May 1995 (Box 12)
    - California April 1998 (Box 12)
    - California April-May 1999 (Box 12)
  - Personal events
    - Anniversary parties and other events 1977-1983 (Box 12)
      (originally labeled "Entertainment")
    - Anniversary party August 15, 1986 (Box 12)
    - Birthday party, Hunters Creek Club November 10, 1991 (Box 12)
    - Land Rover shooting trip September 9, 1992 (Box 12)
    - Birthday party, Hunters Creek Club October 31, 1992 (Box 12)
    - Birthday party, Hunters Creek Club November 6, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Empty house party 2800 Glazier Way, September 25, 1994 (Box 12)
    - Birthday party, dinner at Ernesto's November 7, 1995 (Box 12)
    - South Dakota hunting trip October 20, 1996 (Box 12)
    - Grand Match of Shooting and Field Trials, Greenbrier May 1999 (Box 12)
  - Trips abroad
    - Scotland August 1978 (Box 12)
    - Marrakech Range Rover July 1992 (Box 12)
    - Jaguar/ LeMans 1996 (Box 12)
    - Jaguar/Goodwood/Saab June 1997 (Box 12)
    - Isuzu April 1998 (Box 12)
    - London/Goodwood September 1998 (Box 12)
    - Cunard Classic Car Cruise September-October 1998 (Box 12)
    - Goodwood June 1999 (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous (alphabetical)
    - Boojum Baja Bash April 1995 (Box 12)
    - Cars and Cigar Event December 3, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Chevy Tahoe and Suburban Preview August 1999 (Box 12)
    - Chrysler Road Runner 2000 June 19 96 (Box 12)
    - IAMC Awards/SEMA Show 1999 (Box 12)
    - Indy Viper Meeting 1996 (Box 12)
    - Jaguar Book Tour Information 1999-2000 (Box 12)
    - Meeting with Tanzer in New York September 1999 (Box 12)
    - Meguiar Phoenix trip January 1999 (Box 12)
    - Meguiar's Award April 15, 1999 (Box 12)
    - NADA show and other events January 2000 (Box 12)
      (originally filed under "upcoming events")
    - New York trip February 1998 (Box 12)
    - Roundtable Meeting in Orlando January 2000 (Box 12)
    - Santa Barbara/Buick LeSabre January 1999 (Box 12)
    - World Automotive Congress, Detroit July 1977 (Box 12)
- Awards 1974-2006
  The Awards series consists of information regarding awards that either Davis received for his own work, or that of his magazine as a whole. The series is arranged alphabetically by description.
  The Publicity series includes clippings about Davis or his magazines from various publications. Materials in this series are arranged alphabetically by description.
  - IAMC Awards
    - 1997 (Box 12)
    - 1999 (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous awards 1974-2006, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Moto Awards 1997 (Box 12)
  - University of Michigan Doctor of Humane Letters May 2004 (Box 12)
- Publicity 1965-2000
  - Clippings and correspondence 1969-1976 (Box 13)
  - Magazine issues
    (see also Oversized materials series)
    - Detroit Cigar Lifestyles, Fall 1997 (Box 13)
    - Diversion: For Physicians at Leisure March 1994 (Box 13)
    - Nines: The Saab Club Magazine, January / February 2003 (Box 13)
    - United Airlines Hemispheres January 2000 (Box 13)
  - Newspaper articles 1970-1996 (Box 13)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings 1977-1990 (Box 13)
  - Publicity/promotion: Philadelphia SCCA clippings 1965 (Box 13)
  - Z-D News and People and other clippings 1976-1978 (Box 13)
- Collected materials 1967-2004
  The Collected materials series consists of sets of reference material. The bulk of the series consists of "Car files" presented to reflect their original order. The first section of car files consists of materials for various makes and models of cars, the second section for different groupings of cars, and the third for car races. There is also an "Other materials" series with a mixed of other types of reference materials. The folders in this final subseries are arranged alphabetically by description and did not originally exist as one coherent set of files.
  - Car files, section 1 1967-1972
    - A.C. 289 (Box 13)
    - Adams-Farwell 1906 Model 6-A (Box 13)
    - Alfa Romeo (Box 13)
    - Allegro II (Box 13)
    - Amphicar (Box 13)
    - Aston Martin DBS (Box 13)
    - Auburn (Box 13)
    - Austin (Box 13)
    - Austin Healey Sprite MK IV (Box 13)
    - Austin Mini (Box 13)
    - Auto Union Audi (Box 13)
    - Bertone-Jaguar (Box 13)
    - Bentley Continental (Box 13)
    - Blueprints (Box 13)
    - AMX (Box 13)
    - BMW (Box 13)
    - Bond-Equipe 2-liter (Box 13)
    - Brabham BT24 (Box 13)
    - British Motor Holdings (Box 13)
    - Bugatti (Box 13)
    - Buick (Box 13)
    - Cadillac (Box 13)
    - Camaro (Box 13)
    - Chaparral (Box 13)
    - Chevelle (Box 13)
    - Chevron GT (Box 13)
    - Chevy V8 (Box 13)
    - Citroen (Box 13)
    - Cobra (Box 13)
    - Corvair (Box 13)
    - Corvette (Box 13)
    - Cougar GT (Box 13)
    - DAF (Box 13)
    - Daimler (Box 13)
    - Datsun (Box 13)
    - De Tomaso Mangusta (Box 13)
    - Dodge (Box 13)
    - Duesenberg (Box 13)
    - Fairlane Ranchero (Box 13)
    - Ferrari (Box 13)
    - Ferrari 275 GTB4 (Box 13)
    - Fiat (Box 13)
    - Ford (Box 13)
    - Formula One (Box 13)
    - Formula 2 (Box 13)
    - Fraser GT (Box 13)
    - Hillman (Box 13)
    - Hispano-Suiza (Box 13)
    - Honda (Box 13)
    - Humber Sceptre (Box 13)
    - Jaguar (Box 13)
    - Javelin (Box 13)
    - Jeepster (Box 13)
    - Jensen (Box 13)
    - Jensen Interceptor (Box 13)
    - Lancia Flavia (Box 13)
    - Lancia Flavia GT (Box 13)
    - Lamborghini (Box 13)
    - Land-Rover (Box 13)
    - Lincoln Continental (Box 13)
    - Lola (Box 13)
    - Lotus (Box 13)
    - Mercury Marquis (Box 13)
    - MG (Box 13)
    - Mitsubishi (Box 13)
    - Monteverdi (Box 13)
    - Morgan (Box 13)
    - Morris (Box 13)
    - Moskvich de Luxe (Box 13)
    - Maserati (Box 14)
    - Maltra M530 (Box 14)
    - Maverick (Box 14)
    - Mazda (Box 14)
    - McLaren (Box 14)
    - Mercedes-Benz 1968 (Box 14)
    - NSU (Box 14)
    - Opel (Box 14)
    - Packard (Box 14)
    - Peugeot (Box 14)
    - Pininfarina (Box 14)
    - Plymouth (Box 14)
    - Pontiac Firebird (Box 14)
    - Porsche (Box 14)
    - Rambler (Box 14)
    - Reliant Rebel; Reliant Scimitar (Box 14)
    - Renault (Box 14)
    - Riley (Box 14)
    - Rogue (Box 14)
    - Rolls Royce Silver Shadow (Box 14)
    - Rootes (Box 14)
    - Rover (Box 14)
    - Saab (Box 14)
    - Simca (Box 14)
    - Singer Gazelle (Box 14)
    - Studebaker (Box 14)
    - Sunbeam Rapier (Box 14)
    - Sunbeam Stiletto (Box 14)
    - Toronado (Box 14)
    - Toyota (Box 14)
    - Triumph (Box 14)
    - TVR Tuscan SE (Box 14)
    - Vauxhill (Box 14)
    - Vega (Box 14)
    - Victor 2000 (Box 14)
    - Vixen (Box 14)
    - Volkswagen (Box 14)
    - Volvo 144S (Box 14)
    - Wartburg Knight (Box 14)
    - Wolseley 18/85 (Box 14)
  - Car files, section 2 (topical) 1967-1970
    - Cars of Britain (Box 14)
    - Cars of Eastern Europe (Box 14)
    - Cars of France (Box 14)
    - Cars of Germany (Box 14)
    - Cars of Italy (Box 14)
    - Cars of Japan (Box 14)
    - Cars of Sweden & Holland (Box 14)
    - Classics of the '50's (Box 14)
    - Classics of the '40's (Box 14)
    - Classics (Box 14)
    - Drivers (Box 14)
    - Formula Racing (Box 14)
    - Group test (Box 14)
    - The '67's (Box 14)
    - The '68's (Box 14)
  - Car files, section 3 (races) 1967-1970
    - Belgian GP (Box 14)
    - Brands Hatch Boac 500 (Box 14)
    - British GP (Box 14)
    - Monaco GP (Box 14)
    - Monza 1000 KM (Box 14)
    - Nurburgring (Box 14)
    - Reims 12-hour (Box 14)
    - Silverstone (Box 14)
    - South African Grand Prix (Box 14)
    - Spanish Grand Prix (Box 14)
    - Targa Florio (Box 14)
    - United States GP (Box 14)
    - Canadian GP (Box 14)
    - Daytona 500 (Box 14)
    - Dutch Grand Prix (Box 14)
    - French Grand Prix (Box 14)
    - German GP (Box 14)
    - Indianapolis 500 (Box 14)
    - Italian GP (Box 14)
    - Japanese GP (Box 14)
    - Le Mans 24-hour (Box 14)
    - Mexican GP (Box 14)
    - Mexican 1000 Rally (Box 14)
  - Other materials
    - Automotive Hall of Fame 1997 (Box 14)
    - Automobile Magazine (French publication), 1990 (Box 14)
    - BMW Zentrum 2002/EUROFEST 2000 (Box 14)
    - Chevrolet, Louis articles 1940-1967 (Box 14)
    - Communication Arts, 1973 (Box 14)
    - DeLorean material 1973-1983, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Electric car 1990 (Box 15)
    - Marketing reference material circa 1980 (Box 15)
    - Maps, etc. circa 1965 (Box 15)
      (in folder for "Internationale Verkehrsausstellung, München 1965")
    - Mercedes-Benz 220D 1978 (Box 15)
    - Mercedes-Benz Bible June 8, 1965 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous articles/clippings
      - Articles of interest -- DED 1990 (Box 15)
      - Clippings for story research 1985-1990 (Box 15)
      - Unlabeled clippings 1967-1970, 3 folders (Box 15)
      - Unlabeled clippings 1986 (Box 15)
    - Motor Trend articles 2004 (Box 15)
    - Murphy, Thomas speech 1980 (Box 15)
    - New Yorker editorial and advertising summaries 1968 (Box 15)
    - Norman, Geoff: Introduction to Feeling Good, circa 1976 (Box 15)
    - Red Saab circa 1965 (Box 15)
    - Safety 1964-1967, 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Speeches (Brock Yates, Bob Cook, MPA Presentations) 1973, undated (Box 15)
    - Tilden, Bill articles 1973, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Westinghouse press information 1993 (Box 15)
      (with photographs)
    - Ziff-Davis Intercom (newsletter) 1964-1967 (Box 15)
- Topical files/Miscellaneous 1964-2005
  The Topical files/Miscellaneous series contains materials on particular topics that do not fall into the preceding series, such as Davis's work to commemorate Juan Manuel Fangio or with the Michigan Journalism Fellows program. The series also includes a subseries for interview transcripts and legal cases. The materials are arranged alphabetically by topic or description.
  - Autocar drivers handbook circa 1965 (Box 15)
  - Automotive Steering Committee
    - Basserman's Farewell materials 1999 (Box 15)
    - Memoranda and other materials 1998, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - BMW Roadster Book 1995-1996 (Box 15)
  - The Car the Art 1991 (Box 15)
  - Car Information/Records
    - 39 Chevrolet 1997-1999 (Box 16)
    - Citroen 1985 (Box 16)
    - 1955 Chrysler 300, 1995-1996 (Box 16)
    - 1996 Dodge Viper RT/10, 1995-1996 (Box 16)
    - Fiat Toppolino 1971-1980 (Box 16)
    - 1953 Ford F-100, 1993 (Box 16)
    - 1994 Ford F-150, 1994-1995 (Box 16)
      (also includes materials about the Chevrolet Suburban)
    - Haflinger 1982-1983 (Box 16)
    - Jeep 1978-1982 (Box 16)
    - Kougar-Jaguar 1978-1995 (Box 16)
    - 1994 Porsche 968 Cabriolet, 1994-1995 (Box 16)
  - Children's Charter 1991 (Box 16)
  - China Auto (USA) 1996-1997 (Box 16)
  - Cunningham Project 2000-2001 (Box 16)
  - The Double Gun Journal 1994 (Box 16)
    (related to Michigan Journalism Fellows?)
  - Fangio, Juan Manuel
    - Brochures 1986-1987 (Box 16)
    - "Fangio file," undated (Box 16)
    - Fangio Foundation 1995-1997 (Box 16)
    - Los Amigos Americanos del Museo Juan Manuel Fangio 1992-2000 (Box 16)
    - Mixed materials undated (Box 16)
    - Press release regarding Juan Manuel Fangio statue 2003 (Box 16)
  - Interviews
    - Conducted by David E. Davis
      - Tony Lapine interview undated (Box 16)
      - [A. C.] Spectorsky interview undated (Box 16)
        (see also visual and audio materials series)
      - Bill Ruger interview March 21, 1987, 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Iacocca interview for Motor Trend Classic June 2005 (Box 16)
    - Conducted with David E. Davis
      - "A" and "D" interview undated (Box 16)
      - Larry Leins, Ron Hoff, et al. discussion July 30, 1965 (Box 16)
      - Brock Adams and Terrence Bracy February 1, 1979 (Box 16)
      - Steve Crowley Show, G.M.A. Money segment August 28, 1990 (Box 16)
      - Takehiko Shimizu for Le Volant, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Lecture/column by Matthew Denney circa 1970 (Box 16)
  - Legal cases
    - Nissan Pathfinder litigation 1992-1993 (Box 16)
    - Carroll Shelby, et al. v. Superformance Int'l, Inc. 2002 (Box 16)
    - Toyota law suit 1997 (Box 16)
  - Michigan Journalism Fellows
    - Century Club 1994 (Box 16)
    - Livingston Awards/Board Meeting at Mike Wallace's June 1999 (Box 16)
    - Mixed materials 1993-1999 (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous materials 1969-1983 (Box 16)
  - Motorcycle information 1980-1983 (Box 16)
  - Other Organizations
    - Detroit SCCA (Sports Car Club of America) 1998 (Box 17)
    - Greenfield Village 1989 (Box 17)
    - National Automotive History Collection 1996-1997 (Box 17)
  - Personal name files
    - Bondurant, Bob circa 2000 (Box 17)
    - "Howell letters," 1964-1981 (Box 17)
    - Scott, Mary Lee 2000 (Box 17)
    - Spectorsky, A. C. 1970-1973, undated (Box 17)
  - Pininfarina Co. 1968, 1971 (Box 17)
  - Probe video 1992 (Box 17)
  - Sturm, Ruger and Company 1970-1974 (Box 17)
  - Winchell, Frank 1965-1996 (Box 17)
- Visual and audio materials
  The Visual and Audio materials series includes photographs, slides, and audio tapes of Davis, cars, and events. The materials have been divided into subseries by format.
  - Photographs, negatives, and slides
    - Portraits (Box 17)
    - Receiving awards (Box 17)
    - Informal and in groups (Box 17)
    - Trip to England negatives 1988 (Box 17)
    - Cars and races (Box 17)
    - Foto Tillous (Box 17)
    - Snapshots (Box 17)
    - Portrait (Box 17)
      (previously on Maybach speech binder)
    - '39 Chevy and Fangio (Box 17)
    - Fangio museum items 1996 (Box 17)
    - Automobile Magazine European Grand Tour snapshots, circa 1993 (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 18)
  - Audio tapes
    - Barry Farber Show, WOR-FM April 22, 1964 (Box 18)
      (see also Business files series under Car and Driver, Publicity/promotion: Television and Radio)
    - [A. C.] Spectrosky interview, with attached note (Box 18)
      (see also Topical files/Miscellaneous series, under Interviews)
- Removable storage media
  The Removable Storage Media series consists of floppy and zip disks of speeches and other material.
  - DED Speeches (floppy disk) 1996-1999, 1 floppy disks 3.5" (Box 18)
    ("includes Speech template for Quark Copy Desk")
  - Jackie Stewart interview (floppy disk) May 27, 1999, 1 floppy disks 3.5" (Box 18)
  - Toyota/Land Rover Speech (floppy disk) January 14, 2000, 1 floppy disks 3.5" (Box 18)
  - Swedish C of C speech (floppy disk), 1 floppy disks 3.5" (Box 18)
  - NADA Speech draft (floppy disk), 1 floppy disks 3.5" (Box 18)
  - Automobile Magazine -- Fangio with Chevy (zip disk), 1 zip disks (Box 18)
- Oversized materials
  The Oversized materials series contains photographs, a watercolor painting of Davis, and copies of articles.
  - Photographs, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Watercolor (Box 18)
  - Title deed 1972 (Box 18)
  - Magazines and articles 1983-2001 (Box 18)
- Bound magazines 1986-1998
  The Bound Magazines series consists of bound issues of Automobile Magazine from 1986-1998 volumes 1-13. The magazine has been published by Murdoch Magazines (1985-1991) and K-III Magazine Corporation (1991-1998), which was renamed Primedia Consumer Magazines (1998-2007). Under these companies, the magazine was published in New York City. Currently, however, the magazine is published by Source Interlink Media, headquartered in Bonita Springs, Florida. The editorial offices for Automobile Magazine are located in Ann Arbor, Michigan.
  - Automobile Magazine, volumes 1-5, 1986-1990 (Box 19)
  - Automobile Magazine, volumes 5-9, 1990-1994 (Box 20)
  - Automobile Magazine, volumes 9-13, 1994-1998 (Box 21)
- Film
  The Film series contains five 16 mm, one 35 mm, and one 1 inch film reels, two videocassette tapes, and two DVDs of commercials, cars, and David E. Davis television appearances
  - 1974 Chevrolet Dealer Show "Special," Varicom, 16 mm (Reel 1)
  - Auto Collection Dick Robert Film Company, 16 mm (Reel 2)
  - Commercials for Dusseldorf with listing of commercials, 16 mm (Reel 3)
  - [Grand?] Prix Featurette, 35 mm (Reel 4)
  - Untitled, from Mercedes Benz North America (16 mm) (Reel 5)
  - Mercedes Benz, QDAC 5216 Ogilvy & Mather, Syncrofilm Distribution Services (16 mm)Film (cont.) (Reel 6)
  - AC&R/Respond, Automobile Magazine, Empire Video, February 19. 1986 (1 inch) (Box 22)
  - Automobile Magazine, David E. Davis, Jr. (Videocassette tape) (Box 22)
  - Autoline Detroit, Show #1005 Guests: David E. Davis, Winding Road Magazine, Denis McCluggage, Autoweek, Blue Sky Productions, January 29, 2006 (Videocassette tape) (Box 22)
  - Deadline Now #193, Guests: David E. Davis, Jr. and Sean McAlinden, WGTE Public Media, June 8, 2009, DVD (Box 22)